Guide to the William Hillman Shockley Photographs, 1896-1922 and undated, bulk 1897-1909 RL.01177
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- China: Unidentified Locations, 1896-1899; 43 prints
  One image shows Chinese statesman Li Hongzhang (Li Hung-chang, d. 1901) and various dignitaries, including perhaps William Pritchard Morgan. During this period Li was governor-general of Zhili province, and in 1899 was acting governor-general of the Liangguang provinces, so it is possible this image was taken in one of these places, or in Beijing, where Li often conducted diplomatic business.
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1082)
    Chinese men walking
    院中的男人们
    640
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1083)
    Stone grinding
    石碾子
    672
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1084)
    Laborers working
    工人们在工作
    669
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1085)
    Inside factory
    工厂内部
    665
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1086)
    Westerner standing in field
    外国男子站在田间
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1087)
    Field and mountain
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1088)
    群山和田地
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1089)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1092)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1093.1)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1093.2)
    duplicate of 1093.1
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1094)
    Field, village, and mountain
    群山、田地和村落
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1095.1)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1095.2)
    duplicate of 1095.1
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1096)
    River
    河流
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1097)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1098)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1099)
    Water mill on the side of a river
    河对岸的汲水井
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1100)
    田野中的几个人
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1101)
    Camping
    搭帐篷
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1102)
    Horse-drawn wagons crossing river
    马车涉水过河
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1103)
    Bridge to city gate
    护城河上的桥
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1104)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1105)
    Field and trees
    田地和树林
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1106)
    Man on horse in river
    男人骑马过河
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1107)
    Field and lines of trees
    田地, 树丛
  - Making stocking, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1108)
    织袜子
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1109.1)
    两个男人和他们的马匹
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1109.2)
    duplicate of 1109.1
  - Not Peking, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1110)
    不是北京
    Corner of city wall
    城墙拐角
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1111)
    People in field
    人们在田地间
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1112)
    Chinese statesman Li Hung-chang and various dignitaries, William Pritchard Morgan?
    中国政治家李鸿章和其他贵宾
  - 1897, China (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1113)
    1897 年，中国
    人们在田地工作
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1114.1)
    庙内
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1114.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-1114.1
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1114.3)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1115)
    Street with shops
    沿街的商铺
    Probably Shanghai
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1116.1)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1116.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-1116.1
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1116.3)
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1117)
    Large body of water
    湖面
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1118)
    Small boat alongside a large boat
    大船旁的小船
  - No known title, circa 1897-1899 (Box 5, Print RL01177-P-1119)
- India and Other Southern Asia Locations, 1899-1900; 163 prints
  These photographs, taken during Shockley's travels through India nearby areas in Southern Asia, were chiefly meant to document mica mining operations and laterite mining in Nellore, but as always he took many other images during his travels. These feature landscapes with fields and rivers; boats on the water; and important temples and other tourist landmarks and sights. Two images refer to the "famine works" at Ahmadabad, where starving people were sent to be given rations of rice. Animals featured in this series include a lynx and cheetah, used for hunting; bats; monkeys; and buffaloes. Locations range across North and South India, including Delhi, Agra, Eluru, Nellore, Ahmadabad, Tiruchchirāppalli, and Thanjāvūr. There are also images taken in the Singapore Botanical Gardens and of the harbors of Penang (Malaysia), and Rangoon (Burma, or Myanmar). There are a few images from Sri Lanka (formerly Ceylon).
  Of interest are the many images of people: indigenous men, women, and children, often with their dwellings or camps; local mine workers; western tourists; and English mine supervisors, two of whom are E.H. Sargent and L.L. Wickham. The latter bears a strong resemblance to the uniformed man (in his later years), featured along with his family in the modern 8x10 inch prints of images taken at an unidentified English estate.
  Among Shockley's personal papers is a small (5.5 x 2.5 inches) black leather-bound notebook containing a handwritten index to Shockley's photographs taken in India, Singapore, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, and Burma (Myanmar). On the front flyleaf is written, "Photographs taken in India in Dec 1899 to Feby 1900 by Wm. H. Shockley." The notebook is ruled with red margins, as if for an accounting record book. Index numbers written in the right-hand margin correspond with the numbers written on the photographs, followed by a description of the subject of the photograph. Some descriptions are more complete than others. The notebook is also accompanied by an envelope of small samples of the mineral mica collected by Shockley in India.
  - Personal notebook with index of India and South Asia images, 1899-1900 (Box 16)
  - No known title, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1186)
    Snake charmer, Lucknow
  - Jain Temple at Mt. Abu / see 135, 136, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1187)
    1
  - Sunset at sea Indian Ocean, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1188)
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1189)
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1190)
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1191)
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1192)
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1193)
    9
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1194)
    10
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1195)
    11
  - Botanical Garden Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1196)
    12
  - Bungalow above Penang looking toward Sumatra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1197)
    13
  - Singapore Harbor, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1198)
    14
  - Singapore Harbor, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1199)
    15
  - Watering road in Calcutta, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1200.1)
    Man with bullock cart
  - Watering road in Calcutta, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1200.2)
    duplicate of RL01177-P-1200.1
  - Banyan tree in Calcutta, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1201)
    17
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1202)
    18
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1203)
    19
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1204)
    20
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1205)
    21
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1206)
    22
  - Shui Dragon Pagoda at Rangoon / Priests from Upper Burma, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1207)
    23
  - Dwarf in Shui Dagon Pagoda, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1208)
    24
  - Miss Blanche Baker at Shui Dagon Pagoda, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1209)
    25
  - Entrance to Shui Dagon Pagoda, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1210)
    26
  - Entrance to Shui Dagon Pagoda / The large figures are Leogriffs, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1211)
    27
  - Entrance to Shui Dagon Pagoda / The large figures are Leogriffs, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1212)
    28
  - Near Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1213)
    Trees and sky
    29
  - Near Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1214)
    30
  - Tibetans at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1215)
    31
  - Early morning near Darjeeling looking at Mt. Everest, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1216)
    33
  - Tibetans at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1217)
    34
  - Tree Ferns at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1218)
    35
  - Luggage Porter at Darjeeling. This girl was 20 years old. The baggage was loaded on her back by two men., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1219)
    36
  - Market at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1220)
    37
  - Tibetans at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1221)
    38
  - Curio Seller at Darjeeling, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1222)
  - Benares. The large buildings are a sort of clubhouse for natives of Southern India, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1223)
    40
  - Burning ghats Benares. The bodies are cremated here. On shore of Ganges, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1224)
  - Benares. On shore of Ganges, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1225)
  - Benares. On shore of Ganges, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1226)
  - Fakir at Benares, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1227)
    44
  - Monkey Temple Benares, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1228)
    45
  - Snake Charmers at Benares, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1230)
    46
  - Snake Charmer Lucknow, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1231)
    47
  - Private bullock cart at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1232)
    48
  - Tomb at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1233)
  - Taj Mahal at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1234)
    50
  - Taj Mahal at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1235)
    51
  - Taj Mahal at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1236)
    52
  - Taj Mahal at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1237)
  - Decorations, carved marble at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1238)
    54
  - Taj Mahal at Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1239)
  - Gate at Fattepur Sikri, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1240)
    55
  - Houses in Fattepur Sikri, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1241)
  - Houses in Fattepur Sikri, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1242)
  - Tomb of Saint at Fattepur Sikri, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1243)
  - Tomb of Saint at Fattepur Sikri, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1913)
    Detail of interior
    58
  - Steamer Konig Albert Penang Harbor, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1244)
    59
  - Penang Harbor, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1245)
    Two native rowboats with Westerners aboard
  - Railway Station at Tuticorin, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1246)
  - Beach at Colombo, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1247)
  - Talipot Palm at Kandy, Ceylon. This palm when in flower, has a 30 foot blossoming stalk, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1248)
  - Bamboos in Botanical Garden at Perydenia, Ceylon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1249)
    65
  - No known title, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1250)
    Close-up of young Indian man in front of bamboos in botanical garden at Perydenia, Ceylon
    66
  - Talipot Palm at Kandy, Ceylon. This palm when in flower, has a 30 foot blossoming stalk, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1251)
    Indian man standing in front of large palm, holding fruit
    67
  - Rubber trees Perydenia Botanical Gardens, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1252)
    William Shockley in front of large tree
  - Native boats at Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1253)
  - Tuticorin to Colombo steamer, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1254)
    Shows many native passengers on the deck
    Shockley's noteboook lists this print as number 71, but the number on the photograph is 72. The next print is labeled 78. There are no prints or notebook entries for the legacy identifiers 72-77.
  - Mahommedans wrestling at Colombo, Ceylon, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1255)
  - Colombo Steamer Konig Albert in distance, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1256)
    79
  - Native boats at Singapore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1257)
    80
  - Bathing tanks in temple at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1258)
    81
  - Towers in temple at Tanjore Southern India, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1259)
    82
  - Details of 82 [refers to previous print 1259], 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1260)
    Temple at Tanjore Southern India
    83
  - Details of tower, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1261)
    84
  - General view of temples at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1262)
    85
  - Bathing tanks in temple at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1263)
    86
  - Tank (water reservoir) at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1264)
    87
  - Girls carrying water in brass vases, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1265)
    88
  - Temple at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1266)
  - "King's" Palace at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1267)
    90
  - Sacred bull: temple at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1268)
    91
  - Cannon at Tanjore, fired once by train of powder 300 yards long; inhabitants, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1269)
    92
  - Cannon at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1270)
  - Temple at Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1271)
  - Temple at Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1272)
    95
  - Children in temple at Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1273)
    96
  - Women washing / Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1274)
    97
  - Women washing / Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1275)
  - Women washing / Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1276)
    99
  - Women washing / Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1277)
    100
  - Entrance to temple, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1278)
  - Details of temple / Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1279)
    102
  - Temple at Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1280)
  - Priest's house Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1281)
    104
  - Temple entrance Trichinopoli, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1282)
    Includes man riding an elephant
  - Bathing tank in temple of Tanjore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1283)
    106
  - Dak bungalow Trichinopoli. Inn for travelers kept up by government furnishes room and bedstead, the traveler must provide food and bedclothing. Servants are always in the house, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1284)
    107
  - Cart of leader of the orchestra to a Majahrajah near Mysore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1285)
    108
  - Cart of leader of the orchestra to a Majahrajah near Mysore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1286)
    109
  - 40 stamp mill at Mysore Mg. Co. Southern India, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1287)
    110
  - Office at Mica mines near Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1288)
    Thatched structure
    Label pasted on back of photograph: "Mica mine Nellore."
  - Hoisting machines / mica mines, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1289)
    Label pasted on back of photograph: "Carrying waste at Mica Mines Nellore."
    112
  - Office mica mines Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1290)
    Distant shot of mining engineers Sargent and Wickham posed with servant, in front of thatched structure
  - Mica mines, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1291)
    Native thatched dwellings
  - Sergeant and Wickham, mica mines Nellore India, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1292)
    Western mining engineers, posing seated, with servant
    These men were both mining engineers overseeing the mica mines in Nellore. Wickham seems to appear in modern copy prints of British family on estate, in this collection.
    115
  - Sorting and cutting mica Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1293)
    Woman, man, and girl posing at work
    116
  - Sorting and cutting mica Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1294)
    117
  - Mica mines Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1295)
  - Mica mines Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1296)
  - Blacksmith's shop / Nellore mica mine, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1297)
    120
  - Buffalo at Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1298)
  - Pigeons at Jaipur, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1914)
    Large plaza
  - Famine works near Ahmadabad. These people brought from a distance get just enough to live on, a pound of rice daily and little else, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1299)
    Men and women working on large site
    Label pasted on back of photograph: "Famine camp at Ahmadabad."
  - Famine works near Ahmadabad. These people brought from a distance get just enough to live on, a pound of rice daily and little else., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1300)
    Distant view of large work site
    124
  - Cutting laterite - Nellore, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1301)
    Men working, Western man observing from above
    125
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1302)
    126
    Subsequent prints with this same title, are all listed in Shockley's India notebook as having the legacy identifier 126.
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1303)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1915)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1304)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1305)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1306)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1307)
  - Rock temple at Ellora, cut from solid stone in place, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1308)
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1916)
    127
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1309)
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1310)
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1311)
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1917)
    131
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1312)
    132
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1313)
    133
  - Interior of another temple cut from solid stone. The pillars are part of the mountain., 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1314)
  - Jain Temple at Mount Abu, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1315)
    135
  - Jain Temple at Mt. Abu, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1316)
  - Jain Temples at Mt. Abu, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1317)
  - Bheel archer, kills peacock and jungle fowl, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1318)
  - Mrs. Shaw in bullock cart at Ajmere (?), 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1319)
    Western woman and group of small Indian children
  - Monkeys at Ahmadabad, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1320)
  - Monkeys at Ahmadabad, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1321)
  - Monkeys at Ahmadabad, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1322)
  - Water carrier at Fattepur Sikri near Agra, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1323)
    141
  - Bats at Ahmadabad, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1324)
  - Bats at Ahmadabad, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1325)
  - Lynx at Jaipur used for hunting gazelles, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1326)
    143
  - Cheetah used for hunting gazelles Jaipur, 1899 December-1900 February (Box 6, Print RL01177-P-1327)
    144